KONSTANTIN ZAMARAEV

NYC, NY 929-236-6108 http://www.linkedin.com/in/zamaraevk zamaraevk@gmail.com

RESULTS ORIENTED FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Dedicated Front-End Developer with over 4 years of development experience in HTML, CSS, Sass, JavaScript; significant developer skills for frameworks including JQuery, Bootstrap, and AngularJS. Experienced with CRM systems and SDLC methodologies for user testing, SQA, and MVC-based implementation. Thrives in a fast paced environment where leadership skills are vital for success.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Freelance – NYC, NY Feb. 2013 - Present

Web Developer

Served as web developer to lead project development for small-business client projects and provided website maintenance

- Designed and developed landing pages/dynamic websites using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Sass and AngularJS
- Implemented fully responsive client websites in the WordPress Content Management System (CMS)
- QA and debugged over 5 client websites
- Performed graphic optimization for mobile Android and Apple devices and tablets
- Collaborated with design and proofing teams to ensure client expectations and satisfaction

AFFINITY SOUTIONS – NYC, NY

Nov. 2014 - Present

E-mail Marketing Specialist

Tasked to manage e-mail marketing development and deployment across multiple clients and end users

- Build code for responsive HTML templates designed to work across 40+ e-mail clients for over 3,000,000 end users
- Plan, execute and manage email marketing campaigns, including audience segmentation and data processing, pre-deployment testing and quality control
- Educate 5 team members to create clear and responsive code for the templates
- Assist account management team with 12 campaign reports monthly
- Correspond with in-house developers, marketing department, and creative department

uTEST – UFA, Russia Jan. 2014 – Nov. 2014

Quality Assurance (QA) Tester

Supported QA team with test cases for different project scopes on mobile platforms

- Tested Yandex web browser from different IP addresses for functionality and debugging
- Communicated with Team Lead and team members to resolve issues including user interface and functionality
- Tracked and reported issues using proprietary internal bug tracking system
- Performed installations for GUI and usability testing, including accessibility for mobile device screen sizes

INFOTECS – UFA, Russia Feb. 2013 – Jun. 2014

Quality Assurance (QA) Tester

Supported QA team with process improvement and development for banks systems

- Created and executed test cases based on user stories for bank systems
- Tracked and reported issues using JIRA (I.e., interface, functionality)
- Provided feedback and recommendations to developers on software functionality
- Attended daily development team scrum meeting consisting of 5 engineers

COMPUTER SKILLS

Programming: HTML, CSS, Sass, jQuery, JavaScript, Ruby, SQL

Frameworks: Bootstrap 3, Foundation, AngularJS, Ruby on Rails, Sinatra, Compass

Tools: Brackets, Sublime Text, Adobe Suite (Photoshop, Illustrator, Dreamweaver), Github, Stack Overflow

Languages: English (ILR 4); Russian (ILR 5)

EDUCATION

Codecademy & Udemy, - (Ruby, Ruby on Rails, PHP, JS, AngularJS)2015Ufa State Petroleum Technological University, Russia – Bachelors of Science2004-2009

Automation of Production Processes